Guide to the Human Rights Campaign records, 1975-2015.
Human Rights Campaign records, 1975-2015
- Series X. Miscellaneous
  - Newspapers and Magazines
    - Gay marriage in the Washington Times, November 19, 2003 (Box 129, Folder 24)
Star quality: Human Rights Campaign 2007 Los Angeles Gala.
The following materials have been cataloged separately and may be found using the online library catalog.
III International Conference on AIDS, June 1-5, 1987 Final Program. Washington Hilton Hotel Washington, D.C., U.S.A.
IV International Conference on AIDS, Book 2. June 15-16, 1988.
Ve conférence internationale sur le SIDA: le défi scientifique et social: programme = V International Conference on AIDS: the scientific and social challenge: programme. June 4-9, 1989 Montreal, Canada.
Bradford, Judith, et al. The 2000 Census and Same-Sex Households: A User's Guide. New York: The National Gay and Lesbian Task Force Policy Institute, et al., 2002.
Capitol Hill: The Newsletter of the Gay Rights National Lobby, 1 issue.
Equality: Human Rights Campaign News about GLBT America. Washington, D.C.: Human Rights Campaign, Fall-Winter '03, Spring-Fall '04, Spring-Winter '05, Winter '06
HRC Quarterly, Fall '96, Winter '97, Summer-Winter '01, Fall-Winter '02, Spring-Summer '03
Labor and Employment Issues Raised by the Growing Incidence of AIDS and HIV infection. Brice A. McDonald, esp. March 4, 1987. Washington D.C.
Johnson, Hans. Wedded to Intolerance: Extremists Lead Nationwide Assault on the Lives of Lesbian and Gay People. Washington, D.C.: Human Rights Campaign, ca.1996.
Lambda Report on Homosexuality, Vol III, Issue 2, 3, 4.
Momentum, 3 issues.
National March on Washington program booklet, 3 issues.
Project Stop the Abortion Ban. S.L.: Fifty plus One, et al., 1998.
Review of the Public Health Service's Response to AIDS. February 1985. Office of Technology Assessment Technical Memorandum.
S. 1220: AIDS Research, Care and Education and Hostile Amendments. 1987.
Signals: A Publication of the Wichita Gay/Lesbian Alliance, 1 issue.
The State of the Family: Laws and Legislation Affecting Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, and Transgender Families, 2002
The State of the Workplace for Gay and Lesbian Americans: Why Congress Should Pass the Employment Non-Discrimination Act. Washington, D.C.: Human Rights Campaign, 1996.
The State of the Workplace for Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender Americans. Washington, D.C.: Human Rights Campaign, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2003, 2004 (5 issues).
Transgender Issues in the Workplace: A Tool for Managers, 2004
Voices: A Publication of Oregon's Right to Privacy, 1 issue.
Wedded to Intolerance: Extremists Lead Nationwide Assault on the Lives of Lesbian and Gay People. Washington, D.C.: Human Rights Campaign, 1997
What is Lesbian and Gay America Thinking?: The First National Survey of Self-Identified Lesbian and Gay Americans. Washington, D.C.: Human Rights Campaign, ca. 1996.